I'm getting a job!
Huh?
I'm serious, yo!
WHAT?!
My eyes were opened up wide
By a scene that rent my heart
See it flitting, flitting through the gaps in your fingers
Stare at the truth as it comes into view
Is what's been built here paradise?
Tumbling down head over heels
Oh, I know this might be a wasteland
But I have to land so I can survive on my own
I have to go now
I vomited up magificent blood
That these flowers I planted here might bloom eternal
I love this hopeless world enough to give
All that my lungs and my legs and my hands have to give for it
And I swear I'll find a dream
That was worth all this sorrow
10 Hours Earlier
FILE: Forgetter Annette
You once asked for a mission
with specific characteristics,
and I finally found you one.
I did?
You did.
You said you wanted something with
little danger to life and limb,
but one that would build experience nonetheless.
Ah, right, I did, didn't I?
This is just grunt work.
Why bother calling me all the way out here
just to give me an odd job
no harder than a spy academy drill?
So you would owe me one.
Did she memorize everything?
She must have looked through my window,
remembered the locations of every item in the room,
then took the traps she triggered when she snuck in
and reset them to their original positions.
Magnificent.
You've improved your skills, Annette.
I've been found, yo!
Was this for training?
Or did you have something you wanted to talk about?
I want some spending money.
I was buying parts for this machine I'm building,
but then my wages ran out.
The mission completion bonuses that get deposited
into your account are fairly substantial.
Well, I want more!
Annette, what would you say to taking on a side job?
I'm getting a job!
Huh?
Hey, Teach, what's this about Annette getting a job?
It's a simple infiltration mission.
A what?
Two years ago,
an enemy spy was dealing drugs out of
the restaurant Annette's going to be working at.
The matter's long since been settled,
but we need to make sure the shop's
back on the straight and narrow.
I suggested that she spend the next two weeks
working there as her cover,
and when I told her she could keep the wages
she earned, she happily accepted.
Th-that all makes sense,
but are you sure this is a good idea?
Forget working, Annette can't even
handle her chores right.
When I told her to wash the windows the other day,
she blew the whole damn frame off.
I asked her to get us some vegetables,
and she started planting seeds.
She did the laundry, and everything
ended up covered in sequins.
Feels like she's gonna mix blasting powder
into the restaurant's food.
Or build a weapon right in the middle of the kitchen.
I don't think things are going to be nearly as bad
as you're making them out to be,
but it would be a good idea to have
at least two people watching over her.
Huh?
Nooooooo!
Yeeeeeeep!
By the way,
I've got another mission, so I won't be helping out.
I'm counting on you.
After Day 1 on the Job
Bluhhhhh...
Yeeeeeep...
Wh-what the hell's goin' on at that restaurant?
Whatever it is, it can't be good.
Bluhhhhh...
Yeeeeeep...
I worked hard today, so I'm gonna drink some milk!
Day 2 on the Job
I'm off to work, yo.
Bluhhhhh...
Yeeeeeep...
H-have a nice day...
That settles it.
No way we're goin' near that restaurant.
Agreed, my life is too precious.
Shit gives me the chills.
Day 3 on the Job
Don't do it!
Your soul will end up screaming "bluhhhhh"!
We're just going to check it out.
Should be worth a solid laugh.
Simple or not, the boss entrusted us with this mission.
We can't afford to slack off.
It's Monika and Grete we're talkin' about.
Maybe they'll be okay.
I certainly hope so.
Gahhhhh...
Urrrrrrgh...
I'm gonna go take a bath to scrub off the grime
from how hard I worked, yo!
Day 4 on the Job
I-it's just up ahead.
I say we turn back!
I don't want to end up turning into a bluhhhhh!
Or an urrrrrrgh!
Or a gluhhhhh!
C'mon, nobody's gone "gluhhhhh" yet!
We gotta find out what's happening.
At this rate, Lamplight's gonna get wiped out!
Y-you're right.
Thank you so much for waiting.
I have your grilled chicken and shrimp fritters.
Please, enjoy.
Excuse me!
Hello there!
Have you decided on your order?
Chef, table two is gonna be
a chickpea salad with no pepper,
garlic toast, a large sirloin pasta,
and they asked to get their coffee
once they’re done with their entrees.
Also, table four still needs their tomato soup,
and table twenty-two needs their cheesecake.
Manager, I went ahead and fixed that
tap with the wonky flow.
I used my special sprayer to clean up
the graffiti in the bathroom.
Oh, mister, welcome back!
Will you be having the usual today?
WE NEED TO SPEAK WITH HER GUARDIAN!
Wh-what's this about?
That's well within Miss Annette's
capabilities, you know.
Wait, what're you talkin' about?
Well, about that...
It's a little difficult to explain,
but it all boils down to how motivated she is.
How motivated she is?
That's right.
She's always been brimming with potential.
She's super smart, and while she
might not show it, she's really adaptable.
But the thing is, and I'm not sure I'm putting it
very well, the issue is with her attitude.
Yeah, she is pretty damn free-spirited.
Whenever she's got her mind set on somethin',
it's like nothin' else even registers to her.
In other words, all that talent is just wasted on her.
You know that if you ask right,
she can do chores just fine, right?
She has a hangup about her height,
so she loves it when you give her
dairy products as a reward.
Ah, that's right.
She did seem kind of torn up
about how she wasn't getting taller.
Isn't it adorable?
Pretty sure you're the only one who sees it that way.
Really?
She's probably responsible for
loads of the foot traffic.
Gotta say, I'm surprised.
That's right.
It makes me realize how shallow I was being.
Hey, you there.
Yes? How can I help you?
This glass is dirty.
Go get me a new one.
That four-eyed piece of shit!
Wait! Have some faith in Annette.
But like...
I'm terribly sorry, sir.
I'll get you that replacement right away.
Damn, she even knows how
to deal with problem customers.
That's the service industry for you, sadly.
No matter how well you do your job,
there's just no pleasing some people.
Still, I'm impressed she was able to
keep it professional there.
I woulda just punched him.
I wonder what she needs the money for, though?
Actually, Miss Annette came to me
for advice the other day.
"What kind of present would Klaus like?" she asked.
You mean, she's workin' to buy a gift for Klaus?
What a surprise.
I'm learning all sorts of new things about her.
Also, is it just me, or are her lookouts
not gettin' any of their work done?
And they said they wanted
their free coffee after the entrée...
Damn it, Silver!
You got our order wrong again!
I'm so sorry!
Yeep!
Are you all right?
How unlucky...
Now that we've solved the mystery of the bwuhhhhhs,
we should get back to worrying about the mission.
How's the infiltration going?
Have you noticed anything out of the ordinary?
One thing that's suspicious is how
my body hasn't been moving right lately.
I spent all day falling over.
Now that you mention it,
the bathroom got covered in graffiti again.
And right after Annette cleaned it all off, too.
I copied it all down, yo!
"Hardened Tower"...
"Dangling Hero"...
I wonder if those are some sort of religious symbols?
"My Long-Range Missile Cannon"
and "Bulging Doohickey" go,
those could be some sort of
secret weapons they're developing in-
It's just slang.
Those are all terms for male genitals.
And you let me say them all out loud?!
It is strange how they reappeared in force
immediately after being erased.
Could it be a code, perhaps?
They told me they knew how
I could get rich, and fast.
And these goods are choice, see.
You're up.
That's dried cannabis.
Go put it back where you found it,
but first, slip a transmitter into the pouch.
FILE: Forgetter Annette
I found the guy who took the pouches.
Sure enough, they're using the toilet
as a dropsite for drug deals.
He says that the prices and amounts for sale
get written on the wall each weekend.
Then, the customers leave behind money
and write how much they want.
A Hardened Tower is one bag,
a Dangling Hero is two bags...
You get the idea.
Later, someone leaves the pot behind in the tank.
Excellent work.
Did he see your face?
Of course not.
I've got a master of disguise with me.
Take a hike.
So, that means we should keep an eye on
anyone who goes to the bathroom a lot.
There are two patrons that seem suspicious.
Sybilla, I'll take the man by the window.
You take the man by the wall.
You got it.
I'm code name Pandemonium,
and it's time I cleaned 'em out.
I'm code name Dreamspeaker,
and it's time to lure them to their ruin.
No dice.
I checked his bag, but it was empty.
He's not our dealer.
My target was clean, too.
I leaned against him and peered in his heart,
but I didn't sense any dastardly desires.
Y-you two are incredible.
The people we need to be looking at are the staff.
Yeep!
Let's see, here.
"Go inspect the storeroom."
Hey, Manager, can we take our breaks now?
You may not!
Do you have any idea how many plates
the two of you have broken?!
What?!
Yeep?!
Manager, things are pretty slow
on the floor right now,
so I'm going to go double-check our inventory!
Oh, how thoughtful.
Go ahead and take those two with you.
All right! I'm off!
Th-the way she treats us is like night and day.
Found 'em!
Now, this locker belongs to-
Y-you found them...
Yeep?
I-I'm done for.
Now I have to k-k-kill you...
Huh? Sis?
I-I need the money for Mom's surgery.
Without that weed, I...
S-someone figured out you needed money
and asked you to be their middleman, right?
Who was it?
I-I don't know.
We only ever communicated by letters
and over the phone.
I'm so done for, I-I-I need to kill you...
I-I'm so sorry.
This is for my mom...
I feel for you,
but there are some things you just can't do.
You can atone for your crimes in jail.
Double yeep!
Wait, did Erna die on us?
I'm not dead!
I told you my body hasn't been
listening to me lately!
How unlucky...
I learned something today.
Hm? What's that?
Making money is hard work, yo.
The way it ended leaves a bit of
a bad taste in my mouth,
but we finished the investigation.
Our mission is complete!
Whoo!
I can't believe they were dealin'
out of the restaurant again.
They were probably doing it
to fund their operations,
but still, that's a bold move for
an Imperial spy to make.
I can't stand the way the culprit
took advantage of the pure way
that young man cared about his mother.
I agree.
And when I think about not just him,
but all the people in the city whose lives
will be ruined by that cannabis,
it really does boil my blood.
Feels like we left the job only half-finished.
I understand how you feel,
but discretion is the better part of valor.
From here on out, it's another team's job to handle.
I'm sure they'll put a group of
specialists on the case.
I gotta say, that was easy as pie!
By day, she's a lovable waitress.
But by night, she's a secret agent
who cracks down on drugs!
She's Lily, pride and joy of the Republic!
You sound even more full of yourself than usual.
She really does.
It hurts to admit it, but we all know
who the star player was this time around.
Wait, yo, are you talking about me?
I'm sorry.
I had you pegged all wrong.
You've got enough talent to
make the rest of us feel jealous.
You're an amazing spy.
I was wondering who it was,
but it's you, from the restaurant.
What, are you bitter that I threw my rum at you?
Planning on hitting me with your umbrella, are we?
If you want to try, then by all means, be my guest.
I'm pretty put out myself.
I wouldn't be if you hadn't erased
that graffiti, you know.
I needed it in order to make the money from my-
Damn you, child.
You're in the same business I am!
Dammit, if I could only see...
But how?
I didn't do anything suspicious.
How could you have known?
I stuck the transmitter on you
'cause I was pissed, yo.
What?
You put a tracker on me because
you were mad I threw my booze at you?
The fact you're attacking me
for being a spy is just a coincidence?
So, wait, you put trackers on
all your problem customers
so you're ready to kill them whenever you want?
I'm code name Forgetter,
and it's time to put it all together, yo.
You're deranged!
That's not how sane people behave!
Where'd you go?
Where are you?
That's enough.
I have to ask.
Are you doing this to protect the restaurant?
Yup!
The whole place is closing down for
the day tomorrow because of this guy.
Just for the record,
eliminating problem customers isn't part of
the waitress job description.
I had no idea, yo!
That was some good work you did.
Here's your next mission.
You're a real slavedriver, you know that?
This is the mission you've been waiting for.
For real, this time.
I figured out why I've been
falling down all the time lately!
I got taller!
That's why my clothes were so tight
and hard to move around in.
I'm finally hitting my growth spurt!
Congratulations!
Congrats!
Thanks to the wages from my job,
it's finally finished!
I call it the Erna Shaving Apparatus!
I'm gonna use it to file down her skull!
Oh hey, Bro!
Here's a bribe.
Please go ahead and turn a blind eye here.
That's what the present was for?
C'mon, Erna! We're gonna use my machine to
take off that new height of yours!
Th-the look in her eyes says she's not joking!
Yeeeeep!
You don't get to leave me behind and
have a growth spurt all on your own!
We've been given our next mission.
After we took Corpse alive, he started talking.
Now, we know where Serpent is lurking.
So? Who you pickin' to come along?
Everyone.
The nine of us are going to figure out
who Serpent really is.
This mission is going to involve
infiltrating a foreign country.
Serpent is hiding in the United States of Mouzaia,
over in the New World.
This is going to be a major trial for all of you.